In the last video we had a look at reactrocks.com,
W ostatnim filmie przyjrzelimy si reakcjom. com, teraz chc
now I want to guide you to this Google search, build with react.
Ci poprowadzi do tej wyszukiwarki Google, buduj z reakcj.
Now this might sound stupid but if you look at it, you will for one find an official link so on the official
Moe to zabrzmie gupio, ale jeli na to spojrzysz, znajdziesz jeden oficjalny link, wic na oficjalnym
react repo where you can find projects that are using react and you can look through that list.
repozytorium repozytorium, w ktrym moesz znale projekty, ktre reaguj i moesz przejrze t list.
Now if you click on one of these projects, you'll be redirected to the page not to the source code.
Teraz, jeli klikniesz jeden z tych projektw, zostaniesz przekierowany na stron, a nie do kodu rdowego.
Still, when I talked about practicing that, this can give you some ideas about what you can build because
Mimo to, kiedy mwiem o wiczeniu, to moe da ci kilka pomysw na temat tego, co moesz zbudowa, poniewa
since all of that here is built with react,
skoro wszystko tutaj jest zbudowane z reakcj, z pewnoci
well you certainly can't find an excuse that you can't do it with react.
nie moesz znale wymwki, e nie moesz tego zrobi z reakcj.
So definitely feel free to play around here and dig into these projects to get an idea about what you
Wic z pewnoci moesz tu zagra i zagbi si w te projekty, aby dowiedzie si,
might build.
co moesz zbudowa.
You will also find more sites when searching for build with react, like madewithreact.com,
Znajdziesz take wicej stron, gdy szukaj kompilacji z reakcj, jak madewithreact. com, moesz to sprawdzi, a
you can also check this out and then find some projects there which you can inspect and there you should
nastpnie znale tam kilka projektw, ktre moesz sprawdzi, i tam
also find the source code for the project.
te powiniene znale kod rdowy projektu.
So that again is another way of really practicing react and digging into other people's projects to
To kolejny sposb na realn reakcj i zagbianie si w projekty innych ludzi, aby dowiedzie
learn how you may improve your code,
si, jak poprawi kod, jednak
however people solved certain problems and so on.
ludzie rozwizali pewne problemy i tak dalej.
So build with react, another great resource to learn more about react and find out how it works.
Wic buduj z reakcj, kolejny wietny zasb, aby dowiedzie si wicej o reakcji i dowiedzie si, jak to dziaa.